I think the world at large can learn a lot from Palestinians, from just the footage that we have watched this week, watching physicians commit themselves to helping people with the literal worst injuries and the worst conditions to help them in.
Watching the civil defense people just tirelessly try and drag people from the rubble.
Watching just, you know, the workers trying to find ways to bring joy to the children and ease their minds in this madness.
Watching everyone, you know, really just pour over each other in love and in support in the face of so much terror.
Watching journalists just tirelessly continue to be a voice for their people, even in the wake of unspeakable tragedy.
So terrifying to be a journalist because you're not just reporting on the suffering of the people, you're also reporting the killing of your friends and your family members.
Heading to the place that got striped and just people gave me these two babies.
Two babies.
And just seeing also the unwavering faith.
They have that even in such darkness, they will see light.
And just seeing also the unwavering faith they have that even in such darkness, they will see light.
The people who are being touted as animals, they are demonstrating for us the most foundational elements of not just what it means to be human, but what it means to be humane.
Free Palestine.
세계 of albeit where the new